Noël Riley Fitch Papers, 1858-2012 (bulk 1965-1995): Finding Aid
Manuscripts Division
Noël Riley Fitch Papers
1858-2012
1965-1995
Manuscripts Division
Fitch, Noël Riley
C0841
39 boxes
2 items
17.4 linear feet
Consists of the writings, correspondence, interviews, printed works, and other additional papers of the American educator and author Noël Riley Fitch (1937- ). Also included are a selection of Sylvia Beach papers that Fitch consulted for her book Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties (1983).
Some of the manuscripts and notes found in draft form in the collection came to print in the following publications: Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties(New York: W. W. Norton, 1983), and Walks in Hemingway's Paris: A Guide for the Literary Traveler(New York: St. Martins, 1990) by Noël Riley Fitch; and Shakespeare and Company (London: Faber and Faber, 1959) by Sylvia Beach.
Researchers working with the papers of Noël Riley Fitch Papers may also be interested to consult the Sylvia Beach Papers (C0108).
Gift of Noël Riley Fitch in several installments, in 1998, 1999, and 2002.
No appraisal information is available.
The audiotapes (cassettes and reel-to-reel) of interviews conducted by Noël Riley Fitch about Sylvia Beach are restricted due to their age and fragile condition. In order to listen to these tapes, researchers must request copies through the Department's duplication process.
This collection primarily consists of papers of Noël Riley Fitch relating to her two books Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties(1983) and Walks in Hemingway's Paris: A Guide for the Literary Traveler(1990), as well as her thesis, dissertation, and other writings about Sylvia Beach (1887-1962), the American proprietress of the bookshop Shakespeare and Company in Paris, France. Included are research files, notes, typescripts, and galleys for Fitch's biography of Beach; correspondence and transcripts of interviews with former friends and associates of Beach, such as Berenice Abbott, Morrill Cody, Malcolm Cowley, Janet Flanner, Marcelle Fournier, Maurice Saillet, and others; correspondence with Richard McDougall, the poet and writer on the life of Adrienne Monnier, and typed copies of McDougall's A Selection of Poems(1957); as well as audiotapes (1969-1982) of Fitch's interviews with Elizabeth Bishop, Frederic Dennis, Helen Eddy, Marthiel Mathews, François Valéry, Priscilla Veitch, and others reminiscing about Beach and Paris in the 1920s and 1930s. There are also notes, manuscript drafts, and galleys of Fitch's Walks in Hemingway's Paris: A Guide for the Literary Traveler, and a cassette tape of an interview with Dutch journalists about the book and Ernest Hemingway (1990). Furthermore, the collection includes articles and book reviews concerning Djuna Barnes; assorted articles and lectures by Fitch; a copy of Lisa MacFarlane's Princeton University thesis on Sylvia Beach entitled "For Who is Silvier" (1979); four unpublished writings by Fitch (1988); additional correspondence between Fitch and her literary agents, friends, and fans primarily relating to Fitch's books concerning Lost Generation authors; and a photograph of photographs hanging in Shakespeare and Company.
The original papers of Sylvia Beach include letters by Beach to her parents and sisters (1898-1952); letters by other family members and friends (1858-1954); a photograph album showing Sylvia and Holly Beach in Italy and Serbia (1917-1920); scrapbook pages of photographs and memorabilia (ca.1932-1949); a typescript draft, with autograph corrections (removed from Fitch's research files), and revised galleys for Beach's book Shakespeare and Company(1959); reviews of the book; cassette tapes of Beach's interview with Jackson Mathews for the Kenyon Review (1960); a scrapbook of obituaries(1962); letters sent to Holly Beach (Mrs. Frederic Dennis) (1962-1964); and correspondence regarding Sylvia Beach's estate (1962-1962).
An additional accession consists of several typescript versions of "Voyage to Ithaca: William Carlos Williams in Paris," with holograph corrections, annotations, and additions by Fitch; and correspondence with Else Albrecht-Carrie, Donald Gallup, James Laughlin, Marilyn V. Schuler, Emily Wallace, and Mrs. William Carlos Williams, regarding the above manuscript, which was published in the Princeton University Library Chronicle (spring 1979).
The collection has been arranged in the following series:
Location of Printed Books Removed for Cataloging
Ex Balzac: La Femme de Trente Ans(1912), front cover torn off, inscribed "To Sylvia with love from Mother, Christmas 1913."
Ex Balzac: Ursule Mirouët(1913), front cover torn torn off, inscribed "Eleanor Beach from Sylvester, Christmas 1913, Princeton."
Ex Balzac: La Fausse Maitresse(1912), poor condition, signed "Sylvia Beach, Princeton, 1915."
Ex Beckett, Samuel and others: Our Exagmination Round His Factification for Incamination of Work in Progress(London: Faber and Faber, 1961), inscribed "For Holly with the ex-publishers love, Sylvia, February 1962."
Ex Beach Comité Walt Whitman de Paris: "Exposition Walt Whitman, du 20 avril au 20 juin 1926" (Paris: Shakespeare and Co., 1926).
Ex Mervine, William M.: Harris, Dunlop, Valentine and Allied Families: Compiled for Mary (Harris) Morris(Philadelphia: Edward S. Paret Co., printed for private circulation only, 1920), copy no. 21 of 100 printed; [Mary (Harris) Morris was SB's aunt, from the library of Holly Beach Dennis].
Ex Archives Record of the Class of Eighteen Hundred and Seventy-Six of Princeton College, No. V. 1876-1891 (Rev. Sylvester W. Beach).
Archives Record of the Class of Eighteen Hundred and Seventy-Six of Princeton University, No. VII. 1876-1901 (Rev. Sylvester W. Beach).
Ex Weld, John: Fly Away Home(Santa Barbara: Mission Pub., 1991), presentation copy to NRF by the author.
Authors, American–20th century–Correspondence.; Authors, American–20th century–Interviews.; Authors, American–20th century–Manuscripts.; Authors, French–20th century–Correspondence.; Authors, French–20th century–Interviews.; Booksellers and bookselling–France–Paris–20th century–Biography.; Booksellers and bookselling–France–Paris–20th century–Interviews.; Bookstores–France–Paris–20th century.; Literary landmarks–France–Paris–20th century.; Poets, American–20th century–Correspondence.; Poets, American–20th century–Manuscripts.; Paris (France)–20th century–Intellectual life.; Audiocassettes.; Correspondence.; Interviews.; Manuscripts.; American literature; Hemingway, Ernest, 1899-1961.; McDougall, Richard.; Shakespeare and Company.; Beach, Sylvia; Beach, Sylvia; Beach, Sylvia
- Series 1: Writings, 1965-1995; 8 boxes
  The audiotapes (cassettes and reel-to-reel) of interviews conducted by Noël Riley Fitch about Sylvia Beach are restricted due to their age and fragile condition. In order to listen to these tapes, researchers must request copies through the Department's duplication process.
  This series consists of writings by Fitch concerning Sylvia Beach, Shakespeare and Company, and Ernest Hemingway. There are autograph and typed manuscripts, as well as related correspondence.
  For Fitch's research files for Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties and other writings, see also Series 6, Additional Papers.
  This series is arranged chronologically by the date of the published work.
  - Who is Sylvia?, 1965; 2 folders (Folder 1-2)
    Contain typed manuscript notes and drafts of Fitch's master's thesis ( Washington State University).
  - An American Bookshop in Paris: The Influence of Sylvia Beach's Shakespeare and Company on American Literature, 1969; 3 folders (Folder 3-5)
    Contain correspondence, notes, and typed drafts of Fitch's Ph.D. dissertation ( Washington State University)
  - Voyage à Ithaque: Shakespeare and Company and the American Expatriates, 1969; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    Typed manuscript, 179 pp., Dept. of English, E. N. C.
  - "Mercure de France", undated; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    Translations from French into English of articles about Sylvia Beac, 1 spiral notebook, AMs, 21 pp.
  - "Fitzgerald / Hemingway Annual", 1976; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    Contains correspondence with Matthew Bruccoli, notes, TMs drafts of "Ernest Hemingway–c/o Shakespeare and Company,".
  - American Women Writers, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    Contains correspondence with Frederick Ungar Publishing, notes, drafts for article on SB (Sylvia Beach.
  - Dictionary of Literary Biography, 1979; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    Contains correspondence with Karen Rood (BC Research), notes, drafts for article on SB.
  - Lonnie E. Evans Books, 1983-1988; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    Contains correspondence, notes, for catalog entries.
  - "The Journal of Library History", 1985-1986; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    Contains correspondence, drafts for article on SB.
  - In Transition: A Paris Anthology, 1989-1990; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    Contains correspondence with Christopher Phillips, notes, drafts of NRF's introduction to the book.
  - A Living of Words, 1991-1995; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    Contains correspondence with Susan Albertine, Susquehanna Univ., notes various drafts of NRF's contribution, "Secular Saint, Sylvia Beach, a Woman of Business in Paris" (various titles).
  - Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties(N.Y.: W. W. Norton), 1983; 4 boxes
    - Outlines, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Timelines, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Endnotes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous notes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Permissions, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Photographs - correspondence, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Bibliography, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Pictures - galleys, etc., dates not examined; 2 folders (Folder 8-9)
    - Shakespeare and Company - library list, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Typed manuscript (chapters 1-17), dates not examined; 5 folders (Folder 1-5)
    - Typed manuscript (chapters 18-20, misc. pages), dates not examined; 2 folders (Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous pictures galleys, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Foul galleys, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Corrected proofs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Extra galleys, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
  - Walks in Hemingway's Paris: A Guide to Paris for the Literary Traveler(N.Y.: St. Martin's, 1990), 1989-1990; 2 boxes
    This was published in Great Britain as Hemingway in Paris: Parisian Walks for the Literary Traveler(Wellingborough: Equation, 1989.)
    - Timelines, notes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Maunscript drafts (AMs and TMs), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Corrected typescript, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Photographs (photocopies), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Last draft (with corrections), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Galleys, dates not examined; 2 folders (Folder 6-7)
    - Reviews, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Related correspondence and miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - "Penultimate version of Hemingway in Paris", dates not examined; 9 folders (Folder 1-9)
      Contains the final TMs, with autograph corrections, ca. 230 pp.
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1970s-1990s; 6 boxes
  This series consists of correspondence primarily related to Fitch's books Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirtiesand Walks in Hemingway's Paris: A Guide to Paris for the Literary Traveler. The files include original letters with some carbons of Fitch's replies, transcripts of interviews, manuscript pages with revisions, photographs, obituaries, clippings, and reviews. There are generally less than 10 letters per file. For additional correspondence, see also Series 6, Additional Papers.
  This series is arranged into four subseries: General, Additional Correspondence, Miscellaneous Correspondence, and Richard McDougall Correspondence and Poetry.
  - Subseries 2A: General, undated; 4 boxes
    Consists of correspondence with many individuals who were part of Sylvia Beach's life such as Berenice Abbott, Richard Adler, Carlos Baker, Djuna Barnes, Sylvester Woodbridge Beach, Simone de Beauvoir, Kay Boyle, Winifred Bryher, Truman Capote, Gordon Craig, Holly Beach Dennis, Gisèle Freund, Stuart Gilbert, Henri Hoppenot, Marianne Moore, Katherine Anne Porter, Howard C. Rice, Allen Tate, and Thornton Wilder, as well as others.
    This subseries is organized alphabetically by correspondent's last name or subject, as appropriate.
    - Abbott, Berenice, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Adler, Richard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Albertine, Susan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - American Literature, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - American Notes and Queries, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - AMS Press, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Auclair, Michelle, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Auden, W. H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Baker, Carlos, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Bandy, W. T., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Baron, Jacques, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Barnes, Djuna, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Bayer, Joella, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Beach, Sylvester Woodbridge, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Beauvoir, Simone de, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Beckett, Samuel, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Berry, Joseph, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - Berzinski, Pat, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 19)
    - Bethell, Adrienne, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 20)
    - Bishop, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 21)
    - Blotner, Joseph, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 22)
    - Bonnei, Terese, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 23)
    - Bonnefoy, Yves, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 24)
    - Boski, Anthell, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 25)
    - Boyle, Kay, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 26)
    - Bradley, William, Mrs., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 27)
    - Briggs, James, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 28)
    - Bruccoli, Matthew J., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 29)
    - Bryan, Mina, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 30)
    - Bryher, Winifred, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 31)
    - Budgen, Frank (Joan), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 32)
    - Butler, Reba, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 33)
    - Callaghan, Morley, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 34)
    - Campbell, Jacqueline, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 35)
    - Capote, Truman, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 36)
    - Carlin, Stanley, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 37)
    - Chamson André, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 38)
    - Cody, Morrill, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 39)
    - Cohn, Alan M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 40)
    - Cole, Nancy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 41)
    - Coleman, Earle E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 42)
    - Connolly, Cyril, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 43)
    - Coope, Geoffrey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 44)
    - Cowan, Dan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 44a)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 45)
    - Craig, Gordon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 46)
    - Crosby, [Mary] Caresse, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 47)
    - Cutler, Margot, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 48)
    - Danby-Smith, Valerie, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 49)
    - Dennis, Frederic Beach, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 50)
    - Dennis, Holly Beach [Mrs. Frederic J. Dennis], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Diamond, David, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Dobson, Silvia, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Dunning, Mary, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Durrell, Lawrence, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Dutch Walking Tour, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Eddy, Helen Jerome, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Ellmann, Richard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Ernlund, Carl, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Faus, Keeler, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Finnegan, Francis, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Flanner, Janet and Hildegard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Florshei,, Richard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Ford, Charles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Ford, Hugh, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Fossum, Kristen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Foster, Joseph, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - Fournier, Marcelle, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    - French Embassy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 19)
    - Friede, Eleanor, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 20)
    - Freund, Gisèle, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 21)
    - Gajdusek, Robert E. [Robin], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 22)
    - Geisel, Theodor, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 23)
    - Gellhorn, Martha, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 24)
    - Gerogiannis, Nicholas, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 25)
    - Gilbert, Stuart, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 26)
    - Gilliam, Florence, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 27)
    - Glasheen, Adaline, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 28)
    - Goldsmith, Lester M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 28a)
    - Gordon, [Caroline], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 29)
    - Gray, William, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 30)
    - Groden, Michael, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 31)
    - Halperin, Elaine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 32)
    - Hanley, Frank, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 33)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 34)
    - Hellman, Lillian, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 35)
    - Hemingway, Hadley [Mowrer, Paul Scott, Mrs.], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 36)
    - Henley, Jean E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 37)
    - Herrick, Eleanor Oldenburger, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 38)
    - Hines, Frank B., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 39)
    - Hinkle, Jim, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 40)
    - Hoppenot, Henri, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 41)
    - Hotchner, A.E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 42)
    - Howes, G.E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 43)
    - Jensen, Denise W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 44)
    - Johnson, Marian Willard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 45)
    - Jolas, Maria, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 46)
    - Katz, Leslie [Eakins Press], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Kaufman, James N., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Kenner, Hugh, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Kert, Bernice, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Killride, Jerry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Knodel, Arthur, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Koestler, Arthur, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Kroll, Ernest, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Lanux, Eyre de, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Lawrence, Jerome, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9a)
    - LeFevre, Karen Burke, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Leinwall, George [James Joyce Foundation], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Léon, Lucie, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Lidderdale, Jane, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Lipman, Debroh S., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Lottman, Herbert R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Loughridge, Nancy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    - Mahoney, Patrick R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 19)
    - Main, Raymond E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 20)
    - Malraux, André, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 21)
    - Manuel, Frank E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 22)
    - Marshall, Herbert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 23)
    - Mathews, Marthiel and Jackson, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 24)
    - Matta, Malitte, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 25)
    - McCoy, Logan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 26)
    - McDonald, Dwight, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 27)
    - McKinnon, Alastair, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 28)
    - Meisel, Donald Morrison, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 29)
    - Mercer, Leigh, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 30)
    - Meyer, Doris, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 31)
    - Michaud, David R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 32)
    - Miller, Henry [see Robitaille, Gerald], dates not examined; 1 box
    - Milligan, Vincent, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 33)
    - Moore, Marianne, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 34)
    - Morton, Brian, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 35)
    - Moschos, Myrsine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 36)
    - Murdock, Iris, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 37)
    - Murray, Natalia Banesi, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 38)
    - Nuzum, Ruth and Wayne, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 39)
    - O'Brien, Justin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 40)
    - Odegaard, Charles E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 41)
    - Orbison family, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 42)
    - Ormrod, R. J., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 43)
    - P.E.N., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 44)
    - Phillips, Frank D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 45)
    - Pilat, Oliver, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Popper, Edwin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Potts, Willard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Presbyterian Historical Society, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Preston, Sylvia, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Princeton Cemetary, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Princeton Historical Society, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Princeton University Library (Richard M. Ludwig), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8a)
    - Reck, Michael, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Reynolds, Michael, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Rice, Howard C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Robitaille, Gerald, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Rogers, W. G., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Root, Waverly, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Roy, Claude, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Saillet, Maurice, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Schaffner, Perdita [Hilda Doolittle's daughter], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - Scherman, David, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    - Schneider, Douglas, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 19)
    - Schwalb, Richard A., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 20)
    - Shattuck, Robert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 21)
    - Seldes, George and Gilbert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 22)
    - Smith, E. Warren, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 23)